But I love helping people. I love the
concept of donating money.
I just can't do it.
I want to, but my mom wouldn't let me.
Every time I even just think about
donating money, she comes out of
nowhere. She's like, "Who who are you
donating to?" I'm like, "Mom, I don't
know. Like, Save the Children
Foundation." She's like, "You don't even
know those children."
Children can be horrible.
Okay, fine, mom. I'll donate to help the
HOSPITALS LIKE FEED AHOS.COM TO HELP out
all the nurses and doctors. And she was
say, "Okay, Jimmy. Okay,
the doctors make more money than you.
They should donate to you, okay? I make
a website. Feed a comedian.com right
now.
She just ills me. You know,
you donate to anyone, you donate to me.
I give a burst to you. Okay?
Can you imagine? I'm on Family Feud.
Steve's like, "Jimmy, what charity you
playing for?" Feed a comedian.com. Um,
all proceeds go to my mom.
My mom's so tight with my money, she
wouldn't even let me buy her something
nice. For last birthday, I bought her a
nice iPad. Brand new iPad. I thought I
was a good Asian son, right? And my
mom's like, "Oh, no. It's too
expensive."
I'm like, "Mom, it's okay. We can afford
it. Just just enjoy the iPad." She was
like, "No, Jimmy, please return it.
Return it and just give me the cash.
[applause]
We're practical. It's about the bottom
line."
See, we live in a very frivolous
society, man. Everybody loves to brag
about how much [__] they have, how much
money they make. We all brag. We're all
guilty of this. We all just do it in
subtle different ways. Like white
people, for example. White people never
brag about how much money they got. They
always just brag about how expensive
their life is.
Like, oh, Joey just started private
school. It's so expensive
and our remodel is totally going over
budget.
Oh, and you wouldn't believe how much
money we spent going to Fiji.
[cheering]
I'm like, "Okay, Katie, I see your
life." Okay. It's a luxurious. Good for
you. Okay.
Black people, on the other hand, a lot
more straightforward. Black people just
tell you exactly how much money they
spent on something. It's great. You guys
seen it? Like my black friends or even
like rappers, right? They love to brag.
They're like, "This car 80,000.
My mama's house $500,000.
This chain a million dollars, man. I'm
like, okay, you clearly don't have your
priorities straight.
But I appreciate the honesty.
People love to brag about how much money
they spent. Asian people, on the other
hand, we do the exact opposite. We love
to brag about how little money we spent
on some [__] because the art is in the
savings. You never pay full price.
Like my mom, her catchphrase is guess
how much.
Guess how much. [applause]
Yeah. [cheering]
People.
You guys ever play guess how much? My
mom will come home with something new
like a watch. She'll be like, "Jimmy,
Jimmy, guess how much? Guess how much."
I'm like, "Mom, I don't know. It's a
very nice watch, like $5,000." And she
was like, "No, [screaming]
it's $200."
Jimmy, "My house? My house? This house?
Guess how much? Guess how much." I'm
like, "Mom, I don't know. You live in a
very nice house. Like a million
dollars." SHE WAS LIKE, "NO, [screaming]
it's half off. Someone died in it."
>> [applause]
>> And if you know the rules of the game,
you always guess high so you make the
other person feel good about their
purchases. Never guess too low. Have you
ever guessed too low? That's the
ultimate insult to an Asian person.
Okay.
One time my mom came home with some new
shoes. I guess too low. I've never seen
her so disappointed in me.
She was like, "Jimmy, Jimmy, guess how
much? Guess how much." I'm like, "Mom, I
don't know. Very nice shoes. Like $200."
She was like, "Oh,
[applause]
do you even know about shoes?
These are $500 Jimmy shoes." Okay.
Better Jimmy than you.
[applause]
That's how we prank people. [applause]
You got to love it, man. I used to be
embarrassed about all these things. I
thought my mom was cheap. She spoke with
an accent. She made me Chinese food. But
when I got older, I realized it's all
those things that made me different is
what makes me interesting. Now, the tide
has turned, man. Everybody want to be
more Asian. I'm telling you.
>> Yeah, that's right. Everybody want to be
BTS.
Everybody want to eat Shaolong Ba.
And every parent I know is trying to
send their kid to Chinese immersion
school just in case we take over this
[__] You know what I mean?
Got to be proud, man. You got to be
proud of how you grew up. Got to be
proud of your parents, right? I'm a good
Asian kid. I'm great to my parents. I'll
never ever disrespect them in front of
them. You know what I mean? Like
I want to give you guys a quick update
on my dad. Yeah. Richard Oang. Yeah. The
superstar in the family. Yeah.
[applause]
I talked about in my last special. He
became an actor, right? Yeah. Yeah. Not
because he loves the art. It's because
it's so easy. You can do it, right?
But now he's doing great. He's very
successful. Okay. He got his whole life
turned around. He got out of retirement.
He's a full-time actor now. And now he
wants to be an influencer.
He just started his own IG account,
which is just a nightmare cuz old people
I feel like they mean well. Okay, like
my dad, he means well, but he just
doesn't know how it works. Like his
first post on Instagram is a very nice
post. A beautiful picture of the sky,
palm trees, birds flying by. I'm like,
"Oh, this is nice." And I scrolled down
to the caption and he wrote, "All lives
matter.
I'm like, "Dad, what the [__] man?"
Like,
you don't even know what that means. Why
would you write that? It was like, I
know my life a matter, your life a
matter, the person's life a matter,
okay? Or life of matter. I'm like, that
is not what it means.
I made him put his account on private,
okay? Just like a good tiger parent
would. [laughter]
cuz we know the rules. Like young
people, we see through the scams of
Instagram, right? Like for example, I
follow a Sports Center. I understand the
first hundred comments are all bots.
They're all fake, right? Because it's
always some IG booty model saying some
stupid [__] like, "Uh, I want something
long and hard."
This is obviously a scam. So, one time I
clicked on it
just to see what's going on. You know
what I mean? Research. I just want to
see. I just want to get to the bottom of
it. So, I clicked on it. I was like,
"Oh, this is obviously a scam. It's this
girl. She's following 7,000 people, but
she only has one follower." And I
clicked on one follower. It's my dad.
You go to any Chinese restaurant,
THERE'S ABOUT 485 ITEMS ON THE MENU,
and there's one dude back there in the
kitchen.
He's not a chef. He's somebody's uncle
from Hong Kong.
and he knows how to make everything in
under 30 seconds. That guy's the real
hero. You know what I mean? He got a
yellow wife beater that he brought from
the old country
just chilling near the walk. Cigarette
in his mouth just like
[applause]
[cheering]
>> [applause]
>> That guy's a gangster, man.
And he just cusses casually in Cantonese
just like
[applause]
[cheering]
any of you guys speak Cantonese here.
>> Couple of you guys. I was born in Hong
Kong. That's my first language. I love
that language, right? I think it's the
most fun language to speak because it's
the most fun language to cuss in. In
Cantonese, you can just like low-key
casually cuss. Like you go to Chinatown,
you see like a nice old man walk by. He
would just be like,
right? That sounds really nice, right?
But what he actually said was like, "Oh,
[__] your mother and hope your whole
family dies."
[cheering]
That's Cony's, man.
You got to love it. You got to love it,
man.
In a relationship, I think it's
important to know how you convey love,
but it's just as important to know how
you receive love. You got to be
vulnerable and let your partner do nice
things for you. See, I'm not very good
at that. I I'm terrible at like directly
asking for things that I want. So,
instead, I just drop little hints.
That's called being passive aggressive.
Don't do that. Don't do that.
Like for example, I love watching these
YouTube videos of Japanese housewives
making bento boxes.
It's very nice, very cute. It's like a
little ASMR, you know, and it's just
really nice. This Japanese woman wakes
up at 6:00 a.m. every day to make her
working husband a bento box. But I can't
ask my venture capitalist girlfriend to
make me a bento [laughter] box. I'm not
an idiot. I'm a sugar baby.
I know my role.
So instead of asking it directly, I just
drop little hints like we'll be sitting
on the couch together. I just pull on my
phone and pretend I accidentally
stumbled onto this video.
I'm like, "Oh, what is this? Bento
boxes?
Oh my god, it's so cute. What is that?"
LIKE A RICE BALL SHAPED like a panda.
Look, look, look, look. Wow. Oh, so she
makes this every day for him.
Wow. She must love him so much.
I thought I was being slick
until she came out to one of my shows
as she heard this joke.
And she was really upset, man. And
rightfully so. I was just up here
talking, right? We went home. We got
into a big fight. She was like, "Babe,
that's bullshit." Okay. Did Romy do
something? Why don't you just ask me
directly? And if you really want
somebody to make you bentle boxes, why
don't you just go find a Japanese woman?
I'm like, babe, I'm I'm I'm sorry you
feel that way. Uh, okay. But I think
you're missing the point. You don't have
to be Japanese to make bento boxing.
That's right. [cheering]
That's right. [applause]
So now I'm making her bento boxes every
day.
It's
>> how I show my love. [applause]
You got to love the people around you.
You got to be nice to the people around
you, your partner, your family, your
friends. You got to keep your day ones
around, man. You know, everybody when I
was coming up in the game, they gave me
this advice. They're like, "Hey, Jimmy,
you want to be successful? hang out with
successful people because birds of a
feather flock together. That's right,
man. That's right. You guys heard this
before, right? It's [__] [__]
Okay,
successful people are so boring. I hung
out with successful people. They got
successful job. They got successful
family. They don't have time to hang out
your mediocre ass.
So, my real advice to everyone is to
find yourself more loser friends.
That's right. That's right. That's
right. All right, I see some of you guys
clapping. The ones that are not, you're
probably the loser friend, which is
fine. I love you. I love you.
[cheering]
I love all my friends, man. All my day
ones, I used to live in a one-bedroom
apartment with three comedians.
>> Yeah, ain't nothing wrong with that. I
was proud of that. It was all good. They
still my close friends. One of my best
friends, his name is Guam. Guam Felix.
Yeah, he's a comedian. Uh he's named
after the island he was born on. Guam.
Like you know you kind of hood when you
name after the island you were born on.
Like if I came out tonight and it
introduced me as Hong Kong Jimmy.
I'll probably be selling drugs outside.
You know what I mean?
But Guam's one of my greatest friends,
man. He's just a good dude. He's just a
happy goaround guy. You know, he trashed
in my living room for months. And I
asked him like, "Hey, Guam, you got any
plans? You going to go get a job or
something?" He was like, "Nah, dog.
I want to get on that government
disability, homie."
And I'm like, "Okay, are you disabled?"
He was like, "Yeah, I think so, dog. I
threw on my back when I was 19, homie."
I'm like, "Okay, you 42 right now. I
don't think that's going to work out for
you."
See, Guam is great. He lives by the
creed where anything good that happens
to him, he makes sure to thank God.
Right? That's great. And anything bad
that happens to him, he makes sure to
blame the government.
It's a great way to live that when you
take zero personal responsibility.
Like he'll say [__] like, "Oh, damn.
They gave me a speeding ticket and took
away my license, dog. You see, that's
how the government [__] you."
I'm like, "No, I'm pretty sure that's
how you [__] yourself."
And then on the positive side, he'll say
things like, "I just want to thank God
cuz he let me stay with you, dog."
[laughter]
I'm like, "No, you should thank me,
[__]
I'LL LET YOU STAY with me. [applause]
>> I love Guam, man. He's just a happy
go-lucky guy. Doesn't have a lot of
ambition in life. His dream in life is
to win the lottery.
His catchphrase is when I win the
lottery.
[laughter]
But he doesn't have good goals for when
he does win the lottery cuz he'll say
like, "When I win the lottery, we going
to the buffet, dog."
I'm like, "WOW, WE DO THAT RIGHT NOW,
BRO."
But Guan was a man of his word. Not only
would he buy lottery tickets, he stood
in line in every single game show in LA
to try to win his lottery. And he
finally got on this game show called
Let's Make a Deal. Have you guys seen
that?
>> Yes. The show that comes on hosted by
Wayne Brady before the Price is Right.
But in order to get on that show, you
have to wear a costume. And Guam is like
a big Pacific Islander brother. So his
costume options were limited.
He could either be Moana
or The Rock, you know. So he decided to
make his own costume. He cut up a blue
bed sheet, draped it over his body, and
then he got a Chinese rice patty hat,
and he just wore it. I'm like, "Wow,
what the fuck?"
What? He dressed up as Ho Chi Min or
some [__]
And he was like, "No, dog. I'm Master
Raiden for Mortal Kombat, homie."
[cheering]
But I'm most proud of the fact that I
finally have an easy Halloween costume.
Some of you guys don't understand a
struggle for an Asian guy when it comes
to Halloween. Our outfits are limited. I
was Bruce Lee for 6 years.
But this last year, I had the best
Halloween costume. All I did, I went to
Amazon, got like a matching like
tracksuit, put three numbers on my
chest, and I found myself an Indian
friend. It was a
It was such a great Squid Game costume.
Somebody came up to me. He's like, "Oh
my god, you look just like the girl in
Squid Games."
[applause]
[cheering] I like, "Oh, Sha,
I'm proud of all the representation out
there, man." That's right. Have you guys
seen the show Silicon Valley? [cheering]
>> Thank you. Thank you. [applause]
Thank you. That was my first big break,
man. I was so grateful to be a part of
that show. But that was a few years ago
and I always felt like I was the only
Asian person representing, right? I felt
so much weight on my shoulder. Like
every year we got very lucky. We're
getting nominated for an Emmy. So we get
to go to a great ceremony. But every
year we knew we're going to lose
because all the good shows have front
row seats. You know, VEP, Game of
Thrones are all here. We're way the [__]
in the back by the exit sign.
But it's okay. Win or lose, I was there
to represent. I made sure I made my
round, say hi to everyone, so they know
there's Asian presence, you know.
That's right. So, one year, one year
after we lost, everybody left. I walked
down the front row to say hi to some of
my favorite actors and I saw some of
them. I'm like, "Oh my god, that's
that's Amelia Clark. That's Khesi.
That's Jon Snow over there." You know,
and then there's Rachel Brashnahan. Do
you guys know who she is?
I love her. She plays the marvelous Miss
Masel. great show, right? It's an
awesome show. [cheering] And I did a
movie with her a few years ago, so I
decided to say hi. I was like, "Oh my
god, Rachel, it's so great to see you.
Congratulations on everything." And she
was like, "Oh, okay."
I'm like, "Okay." She probably just
forgot who I was. I'm like, "Look, we
did a movie like 6 years ago called
Patriots Day. You were awesome in that
movie. I just want to congratulate you
on everything you've done so far." And
she was like, "Oh, yeah, sure."
And I'm like, "Oh, really?
>> [laughter]
>> Is the marvelous Miss Masel a [__]
[applause]
But I wasn't going to act out of pocket.
I was there to represent. [laughter]
So I was very nice. I was just like,
"Oh, it's okay. He just don't remember."
Um, anyways, I just want to congratulate
you, but all the nominations are
marvelous, Miss Masel. You're awesome.
And she was like, "Oh, I'm not Rachel
Brashahan.
>> [cheering]
>> I'm Evan Rachel Wood from Westworld.
[cheering]
And I was like, "Holy [__] I'm the
racist person here.
I think all white people look alike."
[cheering]
Everybody in the front row was judging
me. Jon Stone was staring me down. I'm
like, "YOU'RE A BASTARD. YOU CAN'T EVEN
STARE."
And I didn't know what to do, right? I
was profusely sweating. My face was
flush red. So, I was just like, "Oh my
god, I am so sorry." But either way,
it's so nice to meet you. My name is
Aquafina. And then I just
[applause]
have other representation out there.
Asian people, we don't all look alike
until we need to.
>> I got a girlfriend now.
Thank you.
>> I love her very much, man. She's an
amazing person. She's very successful.
My girlfriend's a venture capitalist.
>> Yeah. [__] jackpot, right? You know,
it's great. It's great. Uh for you guys
that don't know what a venture capital
means, uh it means that I'm the poorest
person she knows.
And what that really means is I'm her
sugar baby. So, it's great. That's
[cheering] right. That's right. Gender
equality. That's what I'm talking about.
It's time for a man to get TAKEN CARE
OF. THAT'S RIGHT. See that brother
high-fiving his girl? Appreciate you,
man. Fellow sugar baby. Come on. That's
right. That's right. I love her, man.
I'm trying to I'm trying to be a better
boyfriend. I'm new to this like
boyfriend stuff, right? I used to take
everything so personally. Like every
time we get into a fight, I'm like,
"Babe, why you why you mad at me?
I'm the perfect boyfriend." [laughter]
Wrong answer,
fellas. Fellas, if your girl's mad at
you, you can't take that [__] personally
because it's not even about you. She
doesn't even know what she's mad about.
You just happen to be there. You know
what I mean? You're a victim of
circumstance, man.
So, it's not your job to engage in an
argument. It's your job to diffuse the
situation. You got to jiu-jitsu that
[__]
until you get to the bottom of the real
prom.
Like the other week, she was mad at me
about something. She was like, "Babe, I
feel like we don't even like go on date
nights anymore." I'm like, "Okay,
I hear you,
but what's really going on?"
And she's like, "Well, sometimes I feel
like you like hanging out your buddies
more than you like hanging out with me."
And I'm like, "Okay,
I hear you.
But what's really going on?"
[applause]
And then she takes a deep breath and she
was like,
[laughter] "Remember last week ON MY
BIRTHDAY, HEATHER BROUGHT A COUSIN AND
SHE DIDN'T EVEN KNOW MY NAME." I WAS
LIKE, "SEE, THAT'S YOUR PROM RIGHT
THERE.
>> [applause]
>> AIN'T GOT NOTHING TO DO with me.
Heather Cousin's a [__] you know. [__]
her, man. Let's focus our energy on her.
I'm trying to be a better communicator,
man. My girl always wants me to talk
about my feelings. She's like, "Babe, I
wish you'd talk about your feelings
more." I'm like, "I feel fine."
What more do you want me to say? I don't
I'm not that emotionally involved. I
don't know what else. I'm fine. But
don't keep asking me that cuz the fifth
time you ask me that, I might not be
fine.
The fifth time you ask me that [__]
some dark [__] is going to come out.
It's like, babe, how are you feeling? I
don't know. I'm angry all the time.
BECAUSE MY DAD YELLED AT ME AFTER PING
PONG PRACTICE.
[applause]
SEE, guys and girls were just different,
man. Girls are so emotionally evolved.
You know, we even hang out different.
One night, I came home early. My girl
was having a girls night at the house.
I've never seen anything like that.
The TV was off. Seven girls sitting in a
circle
making direct eye contact with each
other.
Every candle in the house was lit.
And I walk by, I'm like, "What is this
witchcraft?
And I just backed into my own room.
Fellas, we hang out different guys. When
we hang out, we sit in a straight line.
TV on full blast. Zero eye contact with
each other.
My girl came home early. She was so
confused. She was like, "Babe, you guys
didn't talk for like 6 hours." I'm like,
"Yeah, isn't that [__] awesome?